There was a time when meeting people was very
easy, we used to meet without hesitation, we
could keep the basics and what have we learnt with time.
Time has taught us an important lesson that
safety is more important
here. This shield of safety is not
in everyone's destiny.
Here with all of you, with a price habit, we have
solved this problem by saying a small Namaste.
Where you yourself uploaded the hi-tech
list, ICICI
Lombard provided healthcare needs in
which pass sanitizers and from the village
and many needy people were expecting safety.
ICICI Lombard's initiative Fast
Extra will cover it with happiness in life.
Birthday
wish typist right.
[Music]